Inventory of the Soviet and post-Soviet independent publications collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- ZAVOLZHSKII DEMOKRAT gazeta demokraticheskogo napravleniia. Redaktor: Fedorovskii, V. I. Novokuibyshevsk, RSFSR. 1990-, 1990: no. 1-2 (Box 561)
- ZAVTRA Gazeta gosudarstva Rossiiskogo Gl. redaktor Prokhanov A. Moscow, Russia. 1993-, 1999: no. 47(312) 2000: no. 42(359) (Box 449)
- ZAVTRA Note: The preceding title to Zavtra was Den' (Moscow), housed within this special collection. Offshoots of Zavtra include Armia i Vlast', Den' Literatury, Den' Voina, and Ziuganov, all housed within this special collection., See: Hoover Instituion Library newspaper collection for this title.
- ZAVTRA Vidannia trudovogo kongresu Ikraini Redkollegiia: V. Zhezhera, A. Martsinovs'kii, N. Filipchuk. Kiev, Ukraine. Monthly. 1995, 1995: no. 5 (Box 561)
- ZAVTRASHNIE VEDOMOSTI [s. l.: s. n. ]. 1997-, 1997: no. 1 (Box 561)
- ZBUDINNE hazeta hromads'ko-kul'turnoho ehurtovannia "Polis'se. " Minsk, Byelorussia. Semimonthly. 1989-, 1989: no. 1(7)-3(10) 1990: no. 8(13)-9(14)1991: no. 5(23) 1992: no. 2(42)-12(52), no. 16(56)-22(62)1993: no. 1(63)-10(72) 1994: no. 1/2(73/74) (Box 449)
- ZDRAVYI SMYSL ezhenedel'naia gazeta. Partiia zdravogo smysla. Glavnyi redaktor: Aleksandr Kiiranen. Minsk, Byelorussia. Weekly. 1995?-, 1995: no. 10 1996: no. 12(31)-13(32), no. 15(34), no. 17(36)-18(37), no. 30(49), no. 35(54) (Box 449)
- ZDRAVYI SMYSL plakat-gazeta Konfederatsii anarkho-sindikalistov. Tematicheskoe prilozhenie k zhurnalu "Obshchina. " See also: Obshchina Nad vypuskom rabotali: Buketov, K., et al. Moscow, Russia. 19??-, 1990: no. 1-2, no. 3 (March) (Box 450)
- ZELENAIA GAZETA izdanie Zelenykh Severo-Zapada. Redaktory: Aleksei Gur'nev, Sergei Lisovskii, Aleksei Gorichenskii. St. Peterburg, Russia. 199?-, 1998: no. 2, no. 7-11, one unnumbered issue with headline "Vybory 98 ...," one unnumbered issue with headline "Odezhda ..." (Box 450)
- ZELENAIA NIT' biulleten'. Moscow, Russia. 19??-, 1992: June/July (Box 561)
- ZELENOGRADSKAIA PRAVDA Glavnyi redaktor: R. B. Nemets. Moscow, Russia. 1999-, 1999: no. 1(1) (Box 450)
- ZELENYE TATARII Dvizhenie po zashchite okruzhaiushchei sredy i razvitie Tatarii. [s. l.: s. n. ]. 1989?-, 1989: no. 1 (Box 450)
- ZELENYI DON gazeta ekologicheskogo obshchestva Cherkasskogo okruga Oblasti Voiska Donskogo. Novocherkassk, Russia. 1991-, 1992: no. 9-10 (Box 450)
- ZELENYI DZVIN ekolohichnyi visnyk. L'vov, Ukraine. 1990?-, 1990: no. 4 (Box 561)
- ZELENYI KOLOKOL Kaluzhskii oblastnoi komitet po ekologii i prirodopol'zovaniiu, Filial VNPO "Ekologicheskie resheniia. " Redaktor: Koroleva, O. Kaluga, RSFSR. 19??-, 1991: no. 9(16) (Box 450)
- ZELENYI LISTOK organ ekologo-politicheskogo kluba "Al'ternativa. " Subtitle varies - 1990 no. 6 "nezavisimyi ekologicheskii vestnik. " Redkollegiia: Bukhranov, S., Krivov, S., Liapaev, I., Fomichev, S. Samara/Kuibyshev, RSFSR. 19??-, 1988: no. 3 1990: no. 6 (Box 561)
- ZELENYI LUCH gazeta Rossiiskoi partii zelenykh i Riazanskogo otdeleniia sotsial'no- ekologicheskogo soiuza. Redaktory: Mikhail Panov, Tat'iana Artemkina. Riazan', Russia. 199?-, 1997: no. 1(24)-2(25) 1998: no. 6(41)1999: no. 1(53), no. 4(56) (Box 561)
- ZELENYI MIR ekologiia. problemy i programmy. Izdatel'skii tsentr "Ekopress. " Gl. redaktor: Frantsen, O. A. Moscow, Russia. 1990-, 1990: no. 3, no. 7, no. 14 1991: no. 17/18, no. 21-22, no. 29/30-31/32, no. 37/381992: no. 1/2, no. 5/6(70)-11/12(76) 1996: no. 8(214)1998: no. 14(278) (Box 450)
- ZELENYI PETERBURG informatsionnyi biulleten' "zelenykh" organizatsii Sankt- Peterburga. Redaktsionnaia gruppa: Gushchin V. A., Lustberg A. E., Taratinskii A. G., Shevchuk Iu. S., Knize O., Iasinskii O. Sankt-Peterburg, Russia. 1996-, 1996: no. 1 "probnyi vypusk" (Box 561)
- ZELENYI SVIT vydannia Ukrains'koi ekolohichnoi asotsiatsii. Redaktor: Pryluts'kyi, M. Kiev, Ukraine. 1990-, 1989: no. 1 1990: no. 1-2, no. 4, no. 6, no. 8, no. 10-12, no. 14-16 1991: no. 1(17)-2(18), no. 4(20)-5(21), no. 7/8(23/24)-13/14(29/30)1992: no. 3(41)-4(42), no. 7(45)-8(46), no. 11/12(49/50) (Box 450, 561)
- ZELI CESMARTI t'eologiur-sazogadoebrivi zurnali. Tbilisi, Georgia. 1989?-, 1989: no. 3 (Box 561)
- ZEMLIA - NOVYI PORIADOK See: Zemlia (Irkutsk).
- ZEMLIA (Irkutsk) oblastnaia krest'ianskaia gazeta. Title varies: 1999 no. 1 May-June "Zemlia - novyi poriadok" Redaktory: G. Russkikh, A. P. Shakhmatov. Irkutsk, RSFSR. Approx. 2 issue per month. 1990-, 1990: no. 1-2 1991: no. 48(52)1997: no. 2(211)1998: no. 6(218)-7(219) 1999: no. 1(220)-2(221), no. 1 [sic] May-June (Box 450)
- ZEMLIA (Moscow) organ Khristianskogo Patrioticheskogo Soiuza. Otvetstvennyi redaktor: Osipov, V. Moscow, Russia. 1989?-, 1989: no. 10-11 1990: no. 12 (Box 561)
- ZEMLIA (Riga) gazeta soiuza sel'skokhoziaistvennikov Latvii. Continued by: Zemlia Latvii. Riga, Latvia. 1990?-, 1990: no. 2(3)-3(4), no. 19(20)-21(22) 1991: no. 3(30)-6(33), no. 11(38)-13(40), no. 15(42)-16(43), no. 21(48), no. 24(51), no. 28(55)-34(61), no. 37(64)-40(67)1992: no. 1(74), no. 4(77)-5(78), no. 9(82)-16(89) (Box 450/451)
- ZEMLIA BALTII Continues: Zemlia Latvii Redaktor: Zagorovskaia, K. Riga, Latvia. 1992-, 1992: no. 29(102)-30(103), no. 32(105)-49(122), spetsvypusk (November 26) 1993: no. 1(123)-7(129), no. 12(134)-17(139), no. 19(141)-51(173) (Box 451/452)
- ZEMLIA I NEBO izdanie zhenskogo ob"edineniia "Rossiia. " Redaktor: Vasilevskaia, E. Saint Petersburg, Russia. 19??-, 1992: no. 1(7) 1993: no. 2(8)1995: no. 1 (Box 452)
- ZEMLIA I TRUD ezhenedel'naia gazeta profsoiuza rabotnikov agropromyshlennogo kompleksa i Agrarnoi partii Rossii. Glavnyi redaktor: S. Krest'ianinov. Moscow, Russia. Weekly. 199?-, 1995: no. 36(239) 1996: no. 20(275), no. 22(277), no. 27(282) (Box 452)
- ZEMLIA I VOLIA chasopys Ukrains'koi selians'koi demokratychnoi partii. Redaktor: Saliuk, O. L'vov, Ukraine. 1990?-, 1990: no. 1-2 1991: no. 1(4)-3(6), no. 7(10)-17(20), no. 20(23)-22(25), no. 24(27)-27(30)1992: no. 13(69) (Box 452)
- ZEMLIA I VOLIA Redaktor: Idolenko, L. P. Kemerovo, Russia. Monthly?. 19??-, 1992: no. 23(46) (Box 452)
- ZEMLIA LATVII Continues: Zemlia (Riga). Continued by: Zemlia Baltii Redaktor: Zagorovskaia, K. Riga, Latvia. 1992-, 1992: no. 17(90)-23(96), no. 26(99)-28(101) (Box 452/453)
- ZEMLIA MOZHAISKAIA Uchreditel': Mozhaiskii raionnyi komitet KPFR. Redaktor: V. E. Kolienko. Mozhaisk, Russia. 199?-, 1998: no. 1(11)-3(13) (Box 453)
- ZEMLIA ROSSII Politicheskaia ezhemesiachnaia gazeta Redaktor Kovalenko E. I. Sankt-Peterburg, Russia. Monthly. 1994?-, 2003: no. 3(27) (Box 453)
- ZEMLIA ROSSII ezhemesiachnaia molodezhnaia krest'ianskaia gazeta. Krest'ianskaia partiia Rossii. Redaktory: A. I. Kadashov, A. I. Kovalenko, Gleb Zheglov. Sankt-Peterburg, Russia. Monthly. 1992-, 1996: no. 2 (July) 1998: one unnumbered issue (October) with headline "Navodnenie v Sankt-Peterburge .... ", no. 12 (December)1999: no. 8(8)-9(9) (Box 453)
- ZEMLIA RUSSKAIA rossiiskaia gazeta. Gl. redaktor: L. A. Maiboroda. Saint Petersburg, Russia. 1995?-, 1995: no. 1/2, no. 6/7 1996: no. 5/6(12/13)-15/16(22/23), no. 19/20(26/27)-27/28(34/35)1997: no. 1/2(36/37)-11/12(45/46), no. 16/19(50/53)-20/22(54/56) 1998: no. 1/3(60/62)-25/28(84/87)1999: no. 1(88)-3(90) (Box 453)
- ZEMLIAKI gazeta veteranov voiny i truda. Redaktor: Bobrov, V. Kemerovo, RSFSR. Weekly. 1990-, 1992: no. 33(93), no. 48(108) 1993: no. 2(114)-6(118), no. 9(121)-11(123), no. 13(125)-31(143), no. 33(145), no. 35(147)-36(148), no. 43(155)-44(156), no. 46(158), no. 49(161)-50(162)1994: no. 3(167)-6(170), no. 14(178) (Box 453/454)
- ZEMSHCHINA vserossiiskaia gazeta soiuza "Khristianskoe Vozrozhdenie. " Note: subtitle varies: 1990 no. 78 "russkaia gramota," 1995 no. 99/100 "vestnik dvizheniia narodnykh natsionalistov. " Redaktorskaia gruppa: Demin, V. K., Zhmurov, A. P., et al. Moscow, Russia. Semimonthly, 1993- Irregular. 1990-, 1990: no. 1-17, 1991: no. 1(18)-8(25), no. 10(27)-13(30), no. 16(33)-26(43), no. 30(47)-31(48), no. 33(50), no. 51, no. 53-58, no. 61-621992: no. 63-75, no. 78-86, no. 88-91 1993: no. 93-971994: no. 98 1995: no. 99/100-101 (Box 454)
- ZEMSKII SOBOR Literaturno-publitsisticheskoe ptilozhenie k gazete "Veche" Redaktor Glukhov V. V. Sankt-Peterburg, Russia., 1990: no. 1 (Box 454)
- ZEMSKII VYBOR Glavnyi redaktor: N. G. Moiseeva. Sankt-Peterburg, Russia. 199?-, 1996: one unnumbered issue (April) (Box 454)
- ZEMSKOE SOBRANIE oblastnoi ezhenedel'nik. Glavnyi redaktor: Dmitrii Chernyshevskii. Saratov, Russia. Weekly. 1994?-, 1996: no. 29(89) (Box 454)
- ZERKALO (Erevan) nezavisimaia armianskaia gazeta. See also: Zerkalo mirovoi pressy Redkollegiia: Amirkhanian, D. Erevan, Armenia. 19??-, 1991: no. 26(33), no. 37(44) (Box 454)
- ZERKALO (Moscow) nezavisimaia gazeta. Uchreditel': Soiuz kinematografistov SSSR. Moscow, Russia. 1991-, 1991: no. 1-2 (Box 454)
- ZERKALO (Murmansk) daidzhest sovetskoi i zarubezhnoi pressy; mestnaia informatsiia. Ezhemesiachnoe prilozhenie k gazeta "Muranskii stroitel'. " Murmansk, Russia. Monthly. 19??-, 1990: December (Box 454)
- ZERKALO (Sverdlovsk) inform-biulleten'. Obzor otechestvennoi i zarubezhnoi pechati. Sverdlovsk, Russia. 19??-, 1991: no. 1(18)-2(19), no. 5(22) (Box 454)
- ZERKALO (Taldom) ezhenedel'naia nezavisimaia gazeta. Redaktor: Seregin, A. Taldom, Russia. Weekly. 19??-, 1993: no. 12(72) (Box 454)
- ZERKALO MIROVOI PRESSY nezavisimaia armianskaia gazeta. See also: Zerkalo (Erevan) Redkollegiia: Amirkhanian, D. Erevan, Armeniia. 19??-, 1991: no. 24(31) (Box 454)
- ZHELEZNODOROZHNIK KUZBASSA Soiuz trudiashchikhsia Kuzbassa. Redaktor: Gagin, Iu. Kemerovo, RSFSR. 1981-, 1990: no. 9/l0(1370/1371) (Box 454)
- ZHENSHCHINY ROSSII gazeta fraktsii politicheskogo dvizheniia "Zhenshchiny Rossii" gosudarstvennoi dumy RF. Subtitle varies: 1997 no. 4- "vserossiiskaia gazeta. " Gl. redaktor: Grantseva T. Moscow, Russia. Approx. monthly. 1995-, 1995: no. 1-2, no. 5, no. 9-11 1996: no. 1(12)-2(13), no. 81997: no. 1, no. 4, no. 6-12 1998: no. 1- 11/121999: no. 1/2-3/4 (Box 454)
- ZHENSHCHINY ZA MIR V SVOEM OTECHESTVE Redaktory: T. Shumilina, N. Mitina. Moscow, Russia. 199?-, 1996: spetsvypusk no. 2 (June) (Box 454)
- ZHENSKOE CHTENIE Redaktor: Lipovskaia, O. Leningrad, Russia. 1988-, 1988: no. 1-2 (Jan. /Feb. -Mar. /Apr. ), no. 4-5 (Jan. /Apr. -?), no. 6 (spetsial'nyi vypusk) (Box 562)
- ZHENSKOE CHTENIE - DAIDZHEST Redaktor: Lipovskaia, O. Saint Petersburg, Russia. 1988-, 1988: no. 1 (Box 562)
- ZHEREKHOVSHCHINA satiricheskoe prilozhenie k zhurnalu Radikal'naia Tver'. See also: Radikal'naia Tver' Glavnyi redaktor: Boris Gurov. Tver', Russia. 19??-, 199?: no. 1 (Box 562)
- ZHERNOVA Komitet sotsial'noi zashchity svoikh prav. Redaktor: Rebrov, V., Gerasimov, S. Moscow, Russia. 198?-, 1989: no. 1-14 1990: no. 15-241991: no. 25-28 1993: no. 42-44 (Box 562)
- ZHERTVY I PALACHI See: 58-ia palachi i zhertvy.
- ZHITOMIR - CAU - COR ezhenedelnyi Mezhassotsiativnyi Informatsionnyi biulleten' Organizatsii Zhitomirskikh Anarkhistov. Redaktor: Iurii Al'bertovich Anisimov. Zhitomir, Ukraine. Weekly. 1991-, 1991: nedelia pervaia, nedelia chetvetaia (Box 562)
- ZHITTIA I PRATSIIA hazeta profspilok L'vivshchyny. Redaktor: Liakhovych, M. L'vov, Ukraine. Monthly?. 1990-, 1991: no. 16(30), no. 18(32)-19(33), no. 21(35)-24(38), no. 27(41) (Box 454)
- ZHIZN' VOZHDEI hazeta Menskaha addzialen'nia infarmatsyinaha ahentstva "Belsamvydat. " Minsk, Byelorussia. 19??-, 1990: no. 1 (Box 454)
- ZHIZN' ZA TSARIA organ Rossiiskogo Khristiansko-Monarkhicheskogo Soiuza. Subtitle varies: 1996 no. 1/2(10/11)- "Rossiiskii Khristiansko- Monarkhicheskii Soiuz; Evropeiskaia Monarkhicheskaia Assotsiatsiia" Redaktor: Zakatov, A. Moscow, Russia. 1992-, 1992: no. 1 1994: no. 1(2)-2(3)1995: no. 1/2(4/5)-3/4(6/7) 1996: no. 1/2(10/11)-9/10(18/19)1997: no. 1/2(20/23)-5/6(26/27) 1998: no. 28/29 (Box 454)
- ZHODA (Minsk) hromadska-palitychnaia hazeta. Zam. Gl. redaktora Karol' A. Minsk, Byelorussia. 19??-, 1992: no. 1(1)-5(5) 1993: no. 1(7)-15(21) (Box 454)
- ZHORNA Biuletyn ukrainski. Olsztyn, Poland., 1989: no. 1-2 (Box 562)
- ZHURNAL "CHASY" See: CHASY zhurnal.
- ZHURNAL NEZAVISIMYKH MNENII Izdatel' zhurnala: Nikol'skii, V. Pskov, RSFSR. 19??-, 1989/90: no. 3 (Box 562)
- ZIUGANOV See also: Zavtra. Glavnyi redaktor: Aleksandr Prokhanov. Moscow, Russia. 1996?-, 1996: spetsialnyi vypusk (March) (Box 455)
- ZNAMENIE Otv. za vypusk: Efremov, V. Saint Petersburg, Russia. 19??-, 1991: no. 1 (Box 455)
- ZNAMIA DRUZHBY gazeta Navoiiskogo oblastnogo i gorodskogo Sovetov narodnykh deputatov. Gl. redaktor: Zagoskin, I. Navoi, Uzbekistan. 3 issues per week. 1983-, 1992: no. 15(1515) (Box 455)
- ZNAMIA KOMMUNISMA organ naberezhnochelninskogo gorkoma KPRT. Glavnyi redaktor: Mamatov, A. Z. Naberezhnye Chelny, Tatarstan. 199?-, 1995: no. 9/10 (April) (Box 455)
- ZNAMIA MIRA gazeta dukhovnogo edineniia. Redaktor: G. S. Gorchakov. Tomsk, Russia. Monthly?. 1992?-, 1995: no. 5(30) May, no. 6(31) June (Box 455)
- ZNAMIA POBEDY izdanie Russkogo Molodezhnogo Fronta. Glavnyi redaktor: M. Fomin. Sankt-Peterburg, Russia. 199?-, 1995: no. 1 (Box 562)
- ZNAMIA SHAKHTERA organ Mezhdurechenskogo gorodskogo komiteta KPSS i gorodskogo soveta narodnykh deputatov Kemerovskoi oblasti. Redaktor: P. P. Shabrikhin. Mezhdurechensk, Russia. 156 issues per year. 1956-, 1989: no. 93(5137) (Box 455)
- ZNAMIA TREZVOSTI Redaktsionnaia kollegiia: Marina Kuz'mina, Sergei Kuz'min. Koshkovo, Russia. 1999?-, 1996: no. 3 (Box 455)
- ZNANIE-VLAST! organ Narodnogo Dvizheniia "K Bogoderzhaviiu. " See also: Rus' (Moscow) Gl. redaktor: V. A. Zaderei. Moscow, Russia. Biweekly. 1997-, 1997: no. 1-34, no. 36-39 1998: no. 1(40)-2(41), no. 3(43)-22(61), no. 30 [misnumbered] with headline "Khvatit nas durit'!," no. 23(62)-26(65), no. 28(67)-43(82), spetsvypusk with headline "K patriotam Rossii!"1999: no. 1(83)-10(92)-16(98), no. 18(100) (Box 455)
- ZNICH Belorussko-rossiiskaia gazeta. Redaktor: N. P. Masherova. Minsk, Byelorussia. 1995?-, 1995: no. 1-3 1996: no. 16(22), no. 19(25)-23(29)1997: no. 1(30), no. 4(33), no. 8(37)-11(40) 1998: no. 2(42) (Box 455)
- ZOLOTI VORITA nezalezhnyi chasopys v borbi za nezalezhnu Ukrainu. Redaktor: Skachok, P. Kiev, Ukraine. 1990-, 1990: no. 5 (Box 562)
- ZOLOTOE KOL'TSO iaroslavskaia oblastnaia gazeta. Gl. redaktor: Chernykh, B. I. Iaroslavl', Russia. 1990-, 1991: no. 33(46) 1993: no. 39(550) (Box 455)
- ZOLOTOI LEV Izdanie russkoi konservativnoi mysli. Moscow, Russia. 1997?-, 1998: no. 1/2 (Box 563)
- ZONA gazeta neravnodushnykh. Tiumen', RSFSR. 19??-, 19?? one unnumbered and undated issue titled "Proekt lozungov A. Cherepanova" (Box 455)
- ZONA I CHELOVEK ezhenedel'naia gazeta sluzhby po ispravitel'nym delam i sotial'noi reabilitatsii. Redaktor: A. N. Tsakun. Novosibirsk, Russia. Weekly. 19??-, 1992: no. 39(634)-41(636), no. 43(638)-44(639), no. 46(641) 1993: no. 1(642)-5(646), no. 27(688)-28(669), no. 30(671)-34(675), no. 37(678)-38(679), no. 40(681)-45(686), no. 47(688)1994: no. 3(693)-4(693), no. 12(702)-22(712), no. 24(714)-32(722), no. 34(724)-35(725), no. 37(727)-40(730), no. 43(733)-45(735) (Box 562)
- ZONA OTSEPLENIIA nezavisimaia gazeta. Redaktor: S. V. Potutkin. Rostov-na-Donu, Russia. 1990-, 1990: no. 2-3 1991: no. 4-6, spetsvypusk (unnumbered and undated)1992: no. 7 1993: no. 1(8)-2(9)1995: no. 13 (Box 455)
- ZORIA BOGUSLAVSHCHINI Organ Boguslavs'kogo raikomu kompartii Ukraini Redaktor Iarmolenko V. P. Ukraine. Monthly. 1995?-, 1999: no. 1(25)-2(26) 2000: no. 1(29)-6(34) 2001: no. 1(35)-2(36) 2002: no. 2(38)-4(40) 2003: no. 5(45) 2004: no. 1(47) (Box 455)
- ZORIA POLYN' blahodiina hazeta zhytomyrs'koi mis'koi orhanizatsii VDT soiuza "Chernobyl'. " Redaktor: Kulish, A. Zhitomir, Ukraine. 1991-, 1991: no. 1 (Box 563)
- ZOV izdanie Soiuza molodykh kommunistov. Redaktor: Gennad'ev, P. Moscow, Russia. 1990?-, 1990: no. 3-4, no. 6 (Box 563)
- ZOV ezhenedel'nyi vestnik. Vsesoiuznogo obshchestva zashchity zhivotnykh. Gl. redaktor: Baranov, V. Moscow, Russia. Weekly. 1990-, 1991: no. 3(11), no. 15(338) 1992: no. 2(375) (Box 455)
- ZUSTRICH informatsiino-analitychnyi tyzhnevyk Ukrainy. Redaktor: Borzovets', V. Kiev, Ukraine. 19??-, 1992: no. 16-17, no. 19-20 (Box 455)
- ZVAZHAI chasapis Belaruskikh Veteranau. Vydae kamitet zyviazi byushikh Belaruskikh Vaiskutsau. Toronto, Canada. Quarterly. 19??-, 1989: no. 3(55) 1991: no. 3(63) (Box 455)
- ZVENIGORODSKIE VEDOMOSTI Gl. redaktor: Krasnov, O. Zvenigorod, RSFSR. Semimonthly. 1991-, 1992: no. 12/15(25/28)-16/19(29/32) (Box 455)
- ZVEZDA narodnaia gazeta Prikam'ia. Redaktor: Trshnikov, S. Perm', Russia. 5 issues per week. 1917-, 1993: no. 92(22354) (Box 455)
- ZVEZDA POVOLZH'IA nezavisimaia gazeta Redaktor G. Selektor. Kazan, Russia. (Box 458)
- ZVEZDA (S Peterburg) Spetsial'nyi vypusk "Moskovskoi Zastavy" po zaiavke RPK. See also: Moskovskaia Zastava Redaktor: Korneev, A. Saint Petersburg, Russia. 1991?-, 1992: no. 15(47) (Box 455)
- ZVEZDY prilozhenie k gazete "Kuznetskii krai. " Kemerovo, Russia. 19??-, 19??: no. 3(20) (Box 455)
- ZVIAZDA Belaruskaia gazeta Gl. redaktor Narkevich U. Minsk, Belorussia. 250 issues per year. 1917-, 2001: no. 183(24299) (Box 455)
- ZVONOK ZVENIT NA PEREMENU vol'naia narodno-pedagodicheskaia gazeta. Glavnyi redaktor: Nina Evgen'evna Beliakova. Moscow, Russia. 1995?-, 1995: no. 2(4) 1996: no. 1(5) (Box 455)